Guide to the Albert Ellis papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Audio Visual Material, 1953-2007
  - Subseries V.1: Audio cassettes, 1966-2007
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 200)
      (Original Musical Compositions, By Dr. Albert Ellis, 1993 February 1; Original Musical Compositions by Dr Albert Ellis, 1993 February 3)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 200)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 September 6, 1. Man w. pub. Spkg fear & over eatg, 2. part of session, man who must spk as well as others)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Jerry--Male who cn’t get women to bed, 1986 September 26, 2. Male who antagonized 2 male friends by demanding; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (RET Dem, Austin, 1977 February 27; Parent Child Conflicts)(Note around tapes: Dems, No Permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (RET Dems, 3., Columbia, SC, 1977 April 25, 1. Male angry at job rejectors; continued, 2. Woman angry at H, 3., 3. Woman afraid to hurt others)(Note around tapes: Dems, No Permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (RET Dem, Deprsd abt lk of enthusiasm of WF; RET, Indianapolis, 1976 September)(Note around tapes: Dems, No Permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (RET Dem, Therapist who forgets thgs, 1975 December)(Note around tapes: Dems, No Permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (RET Dem, Richie--Anx abt. leavg friends & going East, 1977 RET Dem, 1977 2. Male afrd of pub spkg)(Note around tapes: Dems, No Permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Wkshop, 1991 April 5, 1. Woman who May quit soc. wrk school LFT, 2. Man whose wife is neglectg thr children,angry)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (1991 April 12, Fri Wkshop, 1. Woman who must do well & be lvd, 2. Man panickd abt his panic in subway)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 March 14, 1. Unassertv woman, 2. With Brad Brueder, Male digusted w. conditions interferg w. his being a musician; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 October 31, 1. Male who antagonizes other teachers, 2. Male who is handicapped & wants guaranteed work; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Wkshop, 1985 January 18, yng woman blamed in office; continued Young man afrd. of job rejectn)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 July 6, 1. Jim--Procrastination, 2. Lorinda, Woman failing in tests unfinished)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 September 29, 1. Woman whose children won’t talk to her, 2. Recovering heroin addict, whose ex-wife is vindictive)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 July 19, 1. Woman who feels abandoned if lover leaves, 2. Woman who loses identity whn in a relaship)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 November 10, 1. Deprsd abt WF leaving for Cal. 2. Man angry at ex W for wntg custody of thr child; Fri Workshop, 1995 November 10, 1. Deprsd abt WF leavg for Cal.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 July 10, 1. Woman who ws conned by good friends, 2. Woman who is depressed when daughter is depressed)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 March 13, 1. Male who needs masculine woman, 2. Male who has insomnia; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 August 21, 1. Woman engaged to man with Lou Gehrig’s disease, 2. Woman with prob. hating her boss; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 January 26, 2. Woman who is addicted to her computer)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 February 2, 1. Howard: Fear of rejection by women, 2. Joe: 69 year old man afraid to approach women)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 July 13, 1. Woman hatg self for job & other failures, 2. Man alienated from his mother--only part of session)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 November 2, 1. Woman obsessd w., 2. Woman cn’t tlk to Brother, 3.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 January 17, 1. Tom--Male who cn’t get relaship going bks he is an actor, 2. Jan--Fear of failg in good bus; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 December 8, 1. Gil--Afrd of findg woman to marry & then being rejected, 2. Woman afrd to tell men her real age)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 May 26, 1. Karen--family blames her & she agrees, 2. Sylvia--indecisive, not finished)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 June 2, 1. Ruth, stl obsesd w. divorced H., 2. Male n.g. because his wife is rejecting him)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 September 16, 1. Woman who refused man’s sex advances in her office, 2. Young woman afraid of music auditions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 April 14, 1. Woman who is overeatg, 2. Young woman not exercising; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1999 December 17, 1. Unachvg man, 2. Woman procrastinating)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (1996 July 26, Fri Workshop, 1. Woman w. stage fright, 2. Woman enabling her self-deceivg mother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1987 September 25, 1. Man angry at supervisor & himself, 2. Man failing at winning affection of females he really wants; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 September 1, 1. Man afrd of public performances, 2. Ovewt woman, not recorded)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 May 15, 1. Woman w. lack of schl concentration & harrassg cousin; 2. Shelly--Depressd about Barr-Epstein’s disease)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 July 26, 1. Woman wntg commitment & a child, 2. Woman angry at her son & Husband)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 October 28, 1. Woman whose husband isn’t attracted to her sxly & wants to leave her, 2. Man separated from wife who feels rejected by women)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 August 24, 1. Woman who approached her optometrist, 2. Woman afraid of her fear of dying)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 March 29, 1. Male afrd to p piano in public, 2. Diabetic male overeatg & nt relatg to women)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 October 25, Woman afrd to spk w. her 28yr old son, 2. Woman indecisv abt mry her lver in army)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 February 23, 1. Young woman who May not handle work situation well, 2. Woman who can’t stnd economic deprivation)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 April 3, 1. Woman angry at Br & M, Woman angry at roomates & at obnoxious woman)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 August 19, 1. Woman who is failing in statistics, 2. Roxanne--woman who quit grad school)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 July 21, 1. Woman whose worth depends on art work, 2. Man who must succeed in his bus)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 July 12, 1. Woman resentg her sister & relatives, 2. Man addicted to sex & love)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 April 29, 1. Woman hatg ex H for treatg her & her children badly, 2. Self-hatg woman & her mother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 October 20, 1. Male who must not fall back in REBT, 2. Male who must always be doing thgs)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 December 29, 1. Male afrd of failg psychol. 2. Male afrd of studying poorly)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 February 19, 1. Young woman overatg, 2. Woman unassertive with & angry at boss)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 January 29, 1. Male putting self down for not succeeding as photographer, 2. Male downing himself for failing on a project; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 April 3, 1. Young woman with text anxiety, 2. Young woman indecisive abt vacation in Europe; continued.
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 December 26, 1. Woman obsessed with man who went back to his wife, 2. Woman guilty about not preventg her husband from suffering; blank)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Woman with an alcoholic husband she doesn’t leave, 2. 60 yr old male not committed to succeeding in acting; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1981 July 7; Fri Nite, Ellis, 1)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Friday Night, 1981 October 9)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 August 26, 1. Maggie--Anxious & self-downg, 2. Jackie--Guilty about wanting to get rid of a dog; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 February 10, 1. Young man angry at drunken mother, 2. Woman downing herself for social errors; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 December 2, 1. Woman deprsd abt poor mothering, 2. Woman who is afraid to think against her parents views)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 May 5, 1. Jack: Angry at being done in yrs ago, 2. Woman being criticized by her cousin; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 September 2, 1. Woman who is letting her male friend run their relationship, 2. Man who is indecisive; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 February 9, 1. Woman suffering from loneliness, 2. Woman with feelings of worthlessness)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 October 6, 1. Male whose brother insists he support him, 2. Young woman whose mother opposes her going with a Born Again Christian; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 January 6, 1. Teacher who compulsively does her school work, 2. Woman devastated by losg her lover; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 January 26, 2. Woman anx abt interviews)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1989 December 22, 1. Male procrastinating at law paper, 2. Woman who won’t throw out clothes)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 May 3, 1. Woman who can’t gv up her boyfriend & hurt him, 2. Male who must mk rite decisns)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 December 21, 1. Man who is tkg care of distrbd adoptd child, 2. Dan--Must do better than he’s doing)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 March 22, 1. Woman procrastinatg on job calls, 2. Woman anx abt everythg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 March 24, 1. Woman who won’t meditate or write, 2. Woman whose male friend is gambling & exploiting her; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 April 6, 1. Man whose wife left him 5 wks ago, 2. Man whose wife left him a year ago. Jehovahism)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (1. Man who keeps losing good jobs, 2. Grad student who can’t work on his dissertation, Friday Nite Workshop; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 January 27, 1. Woman who cn’t stnd being stuck in her community--Dorothy, 2. Woman puttg self down because ex-lover denigrated her; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 September 4, 1. Mia: Woman afraid of new relationship, 2. Bob: Man afraid of changing job fields; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1987 May 22, 1. Joyce--Awfulizg about recovered addicts getting AIDS, 2. Sheila, Afraid to be innovatv as a teacher of teachers; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 April 19, 1. Male procrastinatg, 2. Female stressed at work)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 June 21, 1. Woman atty who is daydreamg at wrk, 2. Man w. distrbd son)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 April 7, 1. Carole, upset abt poor mark in art course, 2. Hal--afrd W. will leave him for his poor behavior)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 December 7, 1. Allan, Male who nds approval & has to achieve well, 2. Woman who is paranoid & hostile to people who refuse her; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 February 3, 1. Rosella--Guilty abt nt seeing parents & anx abt their dying, 2. Woman whose father beat her; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1986 September 5, 1. Woman who is ashamed of being a legal secy, 2. Woman who has to help others & is angry whn they don’t accept help; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Wkshop, 1990 June 9, 1. Walter--diseasephobic, 2. Woman angry at Mother for giving money to Brother, Rachel)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 December 7, 1. Man afrd his WF is havg an affair, 2. Woman who works compulsively & cn’t relax)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 July 20, 1. Woman who has a man & a gd job, 2. Self-downg woman, Roxanne)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Wkshop, 1991 November 22, 1. Woman whose friend wont send her a birthday card, 2. Psychiatrist anx abt med. Exam)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Bob--Deprsd abt world & his own life, 2. Carol; 2. Carol, Keeps getting to appointments late)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 January 26, 1. Beth, Anx about job interviews; Fri Workshop, 2. Young woman put down by her mother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 September 7, 1. Ruth, Fr of flg at teachg, 2. Dean--Nt able to exprs hs flgs)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1989 September 22, 1. Kate--Should have left male friend before he left her, 2. Joe--should not have stayed with woman friend 3 yrs; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 March 15, 1. Young woman afrd of flyg, 2. Woman addicted to cookies)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1990 October 19, 1. Woman too old because she’s past fifty, 2. Male w. hassles abt pacemaker)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 January 3, 1. Woman too shy to look for a mate, 2. Woman indecisive abt moving back to N.Y.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 December 27, Severely deprsd lonely male, 2. Man who wants a woman but not to hv a child by her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1989 July 14, 1. Allan--not picking a career or persisting at it, 2. David--Fear of going on vacation; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1988 July 8, 1. Rosella--can she insist on a friendship with a male without sex, 2. Hilda--obsession with "I can’t go to sleep"; continued)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 201)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 January 10, 1. Woman who’s bright daughter is failg at college, 2. Woman who’s friend hates her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 February 11, 1. Male afraid of failg at recording, 2. 18 yr old mother of 6 mos baby, blamg self for babies cryg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 January 13, 1. Man who is rejected by a woman, 2. Woman angry at her nonsupportive woman friends)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 August 4, 1. Male who wnts nonmonog relatnship, 2. Female who is unssertiv & perfectnistic)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 September 8, 1. Woman w. fat stomach & severe emotnl probs, 2. Not recorded)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 August 28, 1. Man obsesd w. dead mother, 2. Hal, therapist who screwd up w. his client)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 March 31, 1. Woman w. insomnia & worry, 2. Woman whose writing is rejected)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 April 14, 1. Woman afrd of test tkg, 2. Woman anx abt obsessions, 3. Jim--Indecisive abt retiring)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 November 1, 3., 1. Woman leadg disorg. Life, 2.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1992 November 13, 1. Complsv tlkg woman whose parents r critical, 2. Woman who hangs on to wrong man friends)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1997 July 26, 1. Woman who procrastinates, 2. Woman angry at drivers)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (1993 August 6, Fri Workshop, 1. Man who won’t go after a job, 2. Man who hs to get wht he wnts fast)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 July 1, 1. Woman blamg self for borderline daughter, 2. Man w. flitting relationships)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 July, 1. Man w. procrastination, 2. Man procrast. on thesis, Tape blank on second side)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Man neglectg conversatn w. Mate, 2. Man failg at making good music records)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 February 23, 1. Woman afrd to look at people, 2. not recorded)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 August 11, 1. Man "Too old" to teach aerobics, 2. Not finished recording)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 August 25, 2. Man who is angry at coworker, 1. physician under stressful situations)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 July 28, 1. Woman with OCD ex-Husband, 2. Woman who has no absorbing interest)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1998 September 18, 1. Woman who cant mk decisions, Youth afrd of wht peple think)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Paranoid woman, 2. Man procrastinating on applying for PhD in psychology)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 April 23, 1. Woman who can’t find right man, 2. Woman staying w. man for 8 yrs)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 October 30, 1. Woman who must find rite career, 2. Woman who is a rat packer)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Robert: self-downg abt nabor’s hostility, 2. Tina--Upset abt co-worker’s hostility)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 July 2, 1. Woman who resists marrying her lover, 2. Woman who is agoraphobic)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 September 15, 1. Woman rejected by her Father, 2. Cecilia, nd to control her love)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 October 13, 1. Woman self downg & putg self down for this, 2. Woman angry at racism & criticism)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1995 January 20, Male betrayed by a woman, 2. Male afrd of speaking up in social grps)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1991 December 23, 1. Cecilia, Worthless when she’s unproductv, 2. Jim-Procrastinatg on apt, work, relatnships)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 May 5, 1. Psychotic male, 2. Woman angry at self & at male friend who doesn’t really love her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (1996 April 19, Fri Workshop, 1. Woman, Susan, who is shy & unassertive, 2. Woman whose family members smoke, Elam)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 March 28, 1. Woman not formg relationships, 2. Male needg other’s approval for achievement)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Laura--Deprsd abt never hvg child, 2. Bernice, Procrastinatg on nursg exams)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 May 28, 1. Man angry at W., 2. Wife of angry man)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 March 26, 1. Woman who cant accept being loved, 2. Woman who is procrastinatg, With Steve Jukas)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Nite Workshop, 1999 December 16, 1. Male who must hv a child, 2. Male angry at society for its neglect; Fri Nite Workshop, 1994 December 16, 1. Male who must hv children, 2. Man angry at soc.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 October 6, 1. Woman failg at jobs, 2. Male tryg to desperately get a job)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Wrkshop, 1995 November 3, 1. Woman self-downing for overeatg, 2. Woman who has to run back to Mother & Brother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Therapist anx abt doing well, 2. Young male w. social anx)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 November 17, 1. Woman with rare disease, 2. Not fully record)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 September 20, 1. Woman angry at others & self, 2. Woman afrd to get close to fmly & to others)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (1996 October 4, Fri Workshop, 1. Male w fear of rejectn, 2. Woman who is unassertive)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1993 May 14, Woman who over spends, 2. Man who must not be angry)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 July 30, 1. Woman who awfulizes abt bad things in a world, 2. Woman afraid of flying)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (1996 March22, Fri Workshop, 1. Male who needs others attention, 2. Woman angry at college mates who steal)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 August 16, 1. Med. student anx abt forgetg, 2. Woman tkg on too much for other people)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 August 2, 1. Self downg shy woman, 2. Taiwanese women afrd to move out from parents in law)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 November 1, 1. Male w. stage fright, 2. Woman afrd to tk gd job)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1. Woman whose adult son ignores her, 2. Young woman avoidg close relatnships)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 March 1, 1. Man angry at lover & himself, 2. Woman angry at self for not dietg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 April 26, 1. Luis--procrastinating on school papers, 2. Ruth--Angry at asst teachers & supervisors)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1995 December 22, 1. Male deprsd abt losg job, 2. Woman w. LFT & anger about work)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1996 May 3, 1. Woman angry at lover, 2. Man angry at sister & himself)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 200 August 11, 1. Woman anx abt being homeless & glty for being irresponsible, 2. Woman angry at mother)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 April 22, 1. Male avoidg math in school, 2. Partial, Male afrd of promotion)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 June 11, 1. Woman afrd of social rejectn, 2. Joe--LFT abt rejectns by women)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 July 23, 1. Sam--woman friend not verbal enough, 2. Man who is indecisive)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 May 6, 1. Woman afraid of being rejected, 2. Male who cn’t find an exciting woman)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1994 May 26, 1. Robin, indecisive abt hvg children, 2. Woman whose lover is nt attendg to her)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (1998 March 13, Fri Workshop, 1. Man w. fear of flying, 2. Man who can’t relax)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 1999 November 5, 1. Woman angry at college administrator, 2. Man anry at bad drivers)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)
      (Fri. Workshop, 2000 May 12, 1. Woman depressed abt death of mother, 2. Man who always gets rejected by women)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 202)